

NGUYEN VAN A

MARKETING MANAGER

Male

May 19, 1992

Hanoi, Vietnam

fb.com/quynhtom design

Take advantages of sales skills & experience and Ut enim ad minima veniam, quis nostrum exercitationem ullam corpo of market to become a professional Sales Staff and bring a lot value to Customers. From that, I will contribute to development of CVPRO Company.

EDUCATION



FOREIGN TRADE UNIVERSITY

major. ipsum was born as a nonsense text. "It's not Latin, though it lo administration

m Sep 2007 - Present

FOREIGN TRADE UNIVERSITY

major. corporate administration

m Sep 2007 - Present

EXPERIENCE



Sep 2007 - Present

CVPRO JSC

Sale Executive

Main responsibilities:

- Write and upload product advertising post via Facebook, Forum...
- Introduce, consult tesque. Nunc and answer customers' queries via phone and email.
- Assist to control goods in and out
- Attend Sales Skill Course in the Company

Recognition and Gains:

- Advertising products of the Company to customers effectively: contribute to a 20% increase in the number of customers within one month of working

Sep 2007 - Present

CVPRO JSC

Sale Executive

Main responsibilities:

- Write and upload product advertising post via Facebook, Forum...
- Introduce, consult products and answer customers' queries via phone and
- Assist to pleasure itself, because it is pleasure, but because goods in and out
- Attend Sales Skill Course in the Company

Recognition and Gains:

- Advertising products of the Company to customers effectively: contribute to a 20% increase in the number of customers within one month of working

ACTIVITIES



Sep 2003 - 2007

CVPRO JSC

Sale Executive

- Write and upload product advertising post via Facebook, Forum...
- Introduce, consult products and answer meaningless window dressing, only there to be decorated by designers' queries via phone and email.
- Assist to control goods in and out
- Attend Sales Skill Course in the Company

CERTIFICATIONS



TOEIC Certificate With Score 800 Issued By CVPRO 2004

HONORS & AWARDS



TOEIC Certificate With Score 800 Issued By CVPRO 2013 - 2014

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION



- Organize monthly events, network with US alumni
- Share how to hunt scholarships and US student's life experiences to all students who have received offers from US antium, totam rem aperiam eaque ipsa, quae ab illo inventore veritatis et quasi architecto

REFERENCES



NGUYEN VAN BINH

director of cvpro jsc

SKILLS





INTERESTS



- Organize monthly events, network with US alumni
- Share how to hunt mco laboris nisi ut aliquip ex ea co and US student's life experiences to all students who have received offers from US universities